var Questions = [
  {
    category: 'History',
    question: 'What was the first capital city of the United States?',
    correct_answer: 'Philadelphia'
  },
  {
    category: 'Animals',
    question: 'The Chihuahua is a breed of dog believed to originate from what country?',
    correct_answer: 'Mexico'
  },
  {
    category: 'Literature',
    question: 'Who Wrote To Kill A Mocking Bird?',
    correct_answer: 'Harper Lee'
  },
  {
    category: 'Geography',
    question: 'What is the largest ocean on planet Earth?',
    correct_answer: 'Pacific Ocean'
  },
  {
    category: 'Geography',
    question: 'Sequoia National Park is located in which U.S. state?',
    correct_answer: 'California'
  },
  {
    category: 'Food',
    question: 'The original Starbucks was established in 1971 in what U.S. city',
    correct_answer: 'Seattle'
  },
  {
    category: 'Television',
    question: 'What is the longest running U.S. primetime television show of all time?',
    correct_answer: 'The Simpsons'
  },
  {
    category: 'Television',
    question: 'Who played the title character in the teen sitcom musical comedy "Hannah Montana"?',
    correct_answer: 'Miley Cyrus'
  },
  {
    category: 'Science',
    question: 'Approximately 2% of all people have what eye color?',
    correct_answer: 'Green'
  },
  {
    category: 'Science',
    question: 'How many pairs of chromosomes are in found in the average human?',
    correct_answer: '23'
  },

  {
    category: 'Music',
    question: 'Award winning Latina pop artist Shakira was born in raised in what Country?',
    correct_answer: 'Colombia'
  },
  {
    category: 'Computers',
    question: 'What does the acronym "lol" stand for when used in phone texts and on the internet?',
    correct_answer: 'Laugh Out Loud'
  },
  {
    category: 'United States',
    question: 'Which major American airline is named after a greek letter?',
    correct_answer: 'Delta'
  },
  {
    category: 'Movies',
    question: "In Disney's 'The Little Mermaid' what is the name of the human that Ariel falls in love with?",
    correct_answer: 'Eric'
  },

  {
    category: 'Movies',
    question: 'The first movie of the Fast and Furious franchise was released in what year?',
    correct_answer: '2001'
  },
  {
    category: 'United States',
    question: 'In 1867 the United States purchased Alaska from what country?',
    correct_answer: 'Russia'
  },
  {
    category: 'Computers',
    question: 'HTML and CSS are computer languages used to create what?',
    correct_answer: 'Websites'
  },
  {
    category: 'Sports',
    question: 'How many super bowls have the Denver Broncos won?',
    correct_answer: '3'
  },
  {
    category: 'Sports',
    question: 'What is the most common type of pitch thrown by pitchers in baseball?',
    correct_answer: 'Fastball'
  },

  {
    category: 'Music',
    question: 'Who is the Canadian singer-songwriter best known for her hit song, "Call Me Maybe"?',
    correct_answer: 'Carly Rae Jepsen'
  },

  {
    category: 'Music',
    question: 'Who is the Canadian singer-songwriter best known for her hit song, "Call Me Maybe"?',
    correct_answer: 'Carly Rae Jepsen'
  },

  {
    category: 'Music',
    question: 'Who is the Canadian singer-songwriter best known for her hit song, "Call Me Maybe"?',
    correct_answer: 'Carly Rae Jepsen'
  },

  {
    category: 'Music',
    question: 'Who is the Canadian singer-songwriter best known for her hit song, "Call Me Maybe"?',
    correct_answer: 'Carly Rae Jepsen'
  },

]
